VINCENT VENET

Financial Controller



06.08.16.22.80 v.venet98@gmail.com Date of birth 5 August 1998 Linkedin

SUMMARY

Highly motivated, hardworking, open-minded and curious. I have been working in a sandwich course for 5 years now, I have been able to adapt to different work environments, I have developed my analytical skills in my core business which is management control but I also added value in the creation of specifications and tools to improve some processes.

SKILLS (V)



Pack Office

Ability to analyse and summarise

Organisational and planning skills

Ability to improve processes

LANGUAGES (=)









HOBBIES



- Gym workout o
 - Motorbike o
 - Guitar •

WORK EXPERIENCE

Program controller - Plastic Omnium, Sainte-Julie

September 2019 - present

- Cash project monitoring (cash in / cash out / invoicing monitoring, etc.)
- Project monitoring (pre-milestones / milestones / ERP, etc.)
- Monthly closures (P&L, details of results, provisions, reinvoicing, etc.)
- Participation in ad hoc studies on different topics

Management and administrative officer - GEFCO, Blyes

June 2017 - June 2019

- Processing and control of purchase/sales invoices
- Implementation of a table of financial indicators
- Restructuring of the administrative flow

EDUCATION

MBA Management Finance (Master's degree), MBway Business School, Lyon September 2020 - present

- Notions in in-depth accounting, performance management, consolidation IFRS standard, financial diagnosis, foreign exchange, risk management
- Participation in a Start-up challenge and a Business game

Accounting and Financial Manager (Bachelor's degree), Pigier School, Lyon September 2017 - July 2020

- Notions in Accounting, Finance, Taxation, Management Control, Management Information Systems, English
- Role-playing and reporting on professional activities
- Participation in a Business game

High School diploma, Lycée de la Plaine de l'Ain, Ambérieu-en-Bugey September 2016 - July 2017